[{"answer": "That won't help.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 6, "question": "What about stronger gun laws?", "qSentId": 5}, {"answer": "Because criminals don't care about the gun laws.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 10, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 9}, {"answer": "No, there was no indication when I was in the case, in the enclosure with Couscous, you know, that -- you know, made me feel uncomfortable or -- you know, I didn't see any type of aggressive behavior or anything that I needed to be worried about while I was in with him.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "Was there anything in your encounter with this particular cat which made you feel that there may be a problem down the line?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "Were there any issues about security, about perhaps the level of training for the staff there?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "He eats about eight pounds of food a day.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "So, Dale, How much food does he eat every day?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Just today.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "Do you have a lion by the tail?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, I really don't know the circumstances but I can tell you that my interaction over at Project Survival Cat Haven, they've been very professional and you know, they've always run their protocol very strictly.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "In terms of the intern who has died here, would you have expected somebody who was simply an intern to be inside the cage?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "Well, you know, Piers, obviously, it's a shock anytime someone loses a life like this.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "And from what have gleaned, what do you think may have happened here?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Well, depending on how long this girl had been there.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "Or would it be a more defensive mechanism if they felt that somebody was intruding into their space?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "Well, the point is, Piers, in the zoological world, they're there.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "What is your answer to people who say they shouldn't be in captivity (INAUDIBLE)?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "You know, my thoughts and prayers go out to the family of this young woman.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "And, Jenny, final word from you?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "It is an interesting moment because there has always been this contingent of civil libertarians in Congress that the military way overstretches their bounds and crosses boundaries in terms of what they can do.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "What is your reaction to what's happening?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Well, that is a good point, Piers.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "What is the difference really, other than drones sound scarier about the ability to use a drone?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "OPPINS: Right.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Because if it is okay to assassinate American citizens in Pakistan for grievous offenses against the state, what is the difference really between doing it there or doing it in Texas?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "That's the issue here is the hedging on that very specific question that most people if you asked them will shake their head and think, my God, of course the government shouldn't be able to do that.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "And that shocked a lot of people, right?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "Well, on the first question, he's definitely worth a biography or two.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "B, what do you think his lasting legacy with Fox News will be?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "They were automatic weapons, had silencers on them.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "For what?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "That I can't answer.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Did you ever kill anyone?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "Right now, the people that are in your circle, are they illegally trafficking guns?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "They have people that are elderly, husband and wife or husband and girlfriend or whatever, in a motor home.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "How do they do it?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "An elderly husband and wife hide guns in their motor home, and drive them up from Florida to New York?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "Two cases.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "So what is an average load?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "They would make 5,000 dollars.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "How much would they make?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "And this happens all the time?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "There's ways.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "How do you communicate with one another to arrange the buy?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "Well, I wanted to put them in jail, I would say yes.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "What do you say?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Life.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "What should they be?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "Life?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Do you think that America, the government, is losing its war on guns?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "Because criminals don't care about the gun laws.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "Any means of transportation, conveyance, planes, trains, automobiles.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "How are these guns run?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "Have you ever ridden a bus?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "Have you never been searched getting on a bus?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "I can't comment on that.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "I mean, is that something you would like to see become illegal?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "We enforce the laws that are on the books.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "I would love to.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "You can't tell me what laws you think this country needs to make the streets safer?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Because we are so few and far between out there.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "No, absolutely not, because I don't -- like if you don't want to have a gun, lord knows I wouldn't want you to have a gun.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "You wouldn't agree with mandating it?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Look, I think it is OK if you want to have background checks on people when they buy and sell a gun.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Do you support universal background checks?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "Because I know that they were already convicted criminals, who were already breaking the law by even owning a gun.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "But how do you know that?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "Because --", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "Why are you so keen to maintain the availability of what many see as a military style assault weapon?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "I don't see them as a military style.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "For the civilian population?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "This is my point.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "Isn't that responsible politics?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "I don't know if I support all of them.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "Do you support all those?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "Because I think if you are not prosecuting the guys that are committing these crimes, if you're not having a background for mental health -- I mean, that is where I look at it and say, when they were dealing with mental health in Washington, D.C. right now, I'm all in favor of that, because there is a huge -- you want to talk about a loop hole, it is not the loop hole to buy guns on the black market that's a threat to this country.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "How do you know?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "I love them both.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "Who do you want to start with?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "I didn't think that that was a good thing to do, because I love George Walker Bush, as you have seen in the tape.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "How did you feel about him attacking the president, the United States in the way that he did?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "Roger Ailes is a genius.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "What do you make of the debate about the affect that Fox News has had on American politics and American society?", "qSentId": 677}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 719, "question": "Is it case of two hopes, no hope and Bob Hope?", "qSentId": 718}, {"answer": "Well, he can, but I don't think he will.", "docId": "130306pmt", "aSentId": 733, "question": "Can he win?", "qSentId": 732}]